Lothy Gresser MBA, MHRM

AKA: Amanda Loth Gresser

awloth@gmail.com | (507) 319-2521

SUMMARY

I am an experienced ServiceNow and process improvement developer/engineer that is focused on creating an environment that the end user will find intuitive, engaging, and informative. It is my goal to automate myself out of a job through sound processes, education, and change management. I strive to be a partner in business to all stakeholders because I believe that friction created by the system is what drives the user away from using the tools put in place for them and will find workarounds or alternatives.

SKILLS

Agile development: capture user stories, define minimum viable product for acceptance criteria, prioritize and maintain a backlog, continual process and product improvement

Chatbot administrator: implementation, maintenance, optimization, knowledge creation and maintenance, natural language optimization

Improvements based on data: create easy to understand reports, analyze data to make better and more informed decisions, create easy to understand dashboard for better and faster service.

Automation: process improvement through understanding and partnership with the business community, create automated workflows for repeatable tasks so technicians can tackle more in complex issues sooner and maintain trust among the end user **Knowledge:** create, maintain, and optimize the knowledgebase with articles so the end user can feel confident in solving the issue on their own.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sumitomo Pharma America, Inc - New York, NY

Formerly: Roivant Sciences and Sumitovant BioPharma

Associate Application Support Engineer

Currently using Tokyo – upgrading to Utah in August, 2023

- -ITSM (Incident, Change, Problem, Major incident management, auto-assignments, escalation process, user maintenance, templates for faster resolution)
- -ITAM (CMDB software, hardware, contracts, assignment to users)
- -Software Asset Management (SAM) Pro (Contract management and software entitlements)
- -Integrations (LDAP, Okta, Active Directory, Zoom, Jira, Azure AD, Intune, 3rd party software, and more)
- -ChatBot through Moveworks (implementation, maintenance, automation, messaging service, approvals, natural language responses)
- -IntegrationHub Pro (Creation and maintenance of flow, process engineering, automations,)
- -Performance analytics (Report creation available on demand, scheduled reports, dashboard)
- -Notifications user friendly notifications using out of the box tools and Javascript
- -Service portal management and development (Design, UX, optimization based on feedback)
- -Service catalog (Creation/maintenance of catalog items and workflows/automations)
- -Application scoping
- -Knowledge (Article creation, update, and versioning. Knowledgebase manager)

March 2021-March 2024

November 2019 -March 2020

ServiceNow Developer, Process Improvement Engineer

- -ITSM
- -CMDB
- -ITBM (now known as Application Portfolio Management) (Ideation management, stories)
- -Event management
- -Room management

Affinity Plus Federal Credit Union - Saint Paul, MN

March 2013-August 2019

ServiceNow Developer, Senior Technical Analyst

(2017 - 2019)

- -ITSM
- -Project management
- -Software implementation
- -SQL database experience
- -SalesForce administrator
- -ThoughtFarmer administrator

HR Assistant (2015 – 2017)

Employee advocate and leadership partner. Establish relationships with employees from point-of-hire to termination.

-Benefits consultation

Member Advisor II (2013 – 2015)

Provide excellent customer service through understanding and partnership to aid members in achieving financial success.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

Master's of Business Administration – Hamline University
Master's of Human Resource Management – Concordia University
Bachelor of Arts – Biology and Education – Hamline University
ITIL Certification - Peoplecert
Data Analyst Certificate - Celonis
Full-stack Web Development Certificate - University of Minnesota / edX
Languages: HTML/CSS, Javascript, NodeJS, BootStrap/JQuery, SQL,